### Vladimir

# **Stepanov**

stepanov.vladimir.in.re@gmail.com https://hartaithan.github.io https://t.me/hartaithan Russia, Yakutsk

#### **About**

I am a frontend developer with a passion for continuous growth and improving my skills to create high-quality and user-friendly products

My journey into development began with writing a small text-based game for Android, which made me realize that programming is what I want to do

With over three years of experience working with frontend frameworks (primarily React, but also with React Native, Vue, and Angular), I have gained skills in creating high-quality and responsive user interfaces. I have worked on a variety of projects, including corporate websites, admin panels, and mobile applications

Additionally, I have experience mentoring colleagues who are at the internship stage, and I am always ready to share my knowledge and experience. I believe that teaching others is a great way to improve my own skills and expand my understanding of the subject

#### **About**

#### **Frontend:**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6+
- TypeScript 4+
- CSS, SCSS, Tailwind
- Responsive Design
- Bootstrap, Mantine, Chakra UI
- shadcn/ui, Framer Motion
- Styled Components, Emotion
- React, Next.js [Pages/App Router]
- Vue 2/3, Vuex, Nuxt.js
- Angular, RxJS, NgRX

- Redux / Toolkit, Mobx, Zustand
- React Hook Form, Formik
- GraphQL, Apollo Client
- Canvas API, Intersection Observer API
- Three JS, React Three Fiber
- Notifications API, Service Workers
- Pagination, Infinite Scroll
- Lazy Loading, Virtualization
- Jest, React Testing Library

#### Mobile:

- Kotlin, Java
- Android SDK, Volley
- React Native
- React Navigation
- Reanimated, Gesture Handler

#### **Backend:**

- NodeJS, ExpressJS
- JWT Tokens, Cookies
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Authentication
- Web Sockets

## **Experience**

October 2023 – present

#### **Dvigus**

Frontend Developer (React)

I was responsible for developing a recruitment management system, which included a web application for operator workflows, integration with a call service,

and an admin panel

June 2022 - August 2023

## Qwantum

(1 year 1 month)

Frontend Developer (React, Next.JS, React Native)

I was part of the team developing a C2B2C platform, where I led the development of the client-oriented parts, including a Next.js web application and a React

Native mobile app

May 2021 - May 2022

**AEBIT** 

(1 year)

Frontend Developer (React, Next.JS)

As part of the team, I developed a medical portal on Next.js and its admin panel

on React

Education

2015 - 2018

Yakutsk College of Communications and Energy (YCCE)

Audio-visual technology